//Questions and Options array

const quizArray = [
    {
        id: "0",
        question: "Which is the most widely spoken language in the world?",
        options: ["Spanish", "Mandarin", "English", "German"],
        correct: "Mandarin",
    },
    {
        id: "1",
        question: "Which is the only continent in the world without a desert?",
        options: ["North America", "Asia", "Africa", "Europe"],
        correct: "Europe",
    },
    {
        id: "2",
        question: "Who invented Computer?",
        options: ["Charles Babbage", "Henry Luce", "Henry Babbage", "Charles Luce"],
        correct: "Charles Babbage",
    },
    {
        id: "3",
        question: "What do you call a computer on a network that requests files from another computer?",
        options: ["A client", "A host", "A router", "A web server"],
        correct: "A client",
    },
    {
        id: "4",
        question: "Hardware devices that are not part of the main computer system and are often added later to the system.",
        options: ["Peripheral", "Clip art", "Highlight", "Execute"],
        correct: "Peripheral",
    },
    {
        id: "5",
        question: "The main computer that stores the files that can be sent to computers that are networked together is:",
        options: ["Clip art", "Mother board", "Peripheral", "File server"],
        correct: "File server",
    }, {
        id: "6",
        question: "How can you catch a computer virus?",
        options: ["Sending e-mail messages", "Using a laptop during the winter", "Opening e-mail attachments", "Shopping on-line"],
        correct: "Opening e-mail attachments",
    },
    {
        id: "7",
        question: "Google (www.google.com) is a:",
        options: ["Search Engine", "Number in Math", "Directory of images", "Chat service on the web"],
        correct: "Search Engine",
    },
    {
        id: "8",
        question: "Which is not an Internet protocol?",
        options: ["HTTP", "FTP", "STP", "IP"],
        correct: "STP",
    },
    {
        id: "9",
        question: "Which of the following is not a valid domain name?",
        options: ["www.yahoo.com", "www.yahoo.co.uk", "www.com.yahoo", "www.yahoo.co.in"],
        correct: "www.com.yahoo",
    },
];
